<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Rohit Shinde</title><link>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Rohit Shinde</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 10:21:26 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rohitshinde.in/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Counting Numbers: A Debugging Story</title><link>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/counting-numbers-a-debugging-story/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 10:21:26 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/counting-numbers-a-debugging-story/</guid><description>What is ads? In an ad system, there are three main entities. A business which wants to show an ad to people, the group of people who are eligible to see that ad, and the platform which ties both the parties. The platform generally charges money to businesses based on the number of views, or clicks the ad gets.
Goto is a fat app, and serves many use-cases. You can order food, a ride, or pay for things, and more.</description></item><item><title>A Play With Mental States</title><link>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/a-play-with-mental-states/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 10:59:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/a-play-with-mental-states/</guid><description>Hellooo 💜
Intro This is a story. It has some personal insights. They are worth sharing. I have gone from feeling nothing for a long time to feeling miserable. To feeling great, to feeling miserable again, and so on and so forth like a wave in the last three months. All this started when I decided to step out of the house after having been locked inside for ~2 years of lockdowns.</description></item><item><title>Free will, ego, and morals</title><link>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/free-will-ego-and-morals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 21:40:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/free-will-ego-and-morals/</guid><description>May 2, 2022: I am having second thoughts about this topic. It can become an endless chain of thoughts, not leading to anything of substance. The term &amp;ldquo;free will&amp;rdquo; is hard to define. Also, apparently this post is of low quality (according to /r/philosophy). There are different types of free will that I was not aware of. I will read up on them, and update the post sometime in future.</description></item><item><title>Visualizing time relativeness</title><link>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/visualizing-universe-time-relativeness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:33:53 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rohitshinde.in/blog/visualizing-universe-time-relativeness/</guid><description>What is this? What does a billion years mean to you? Does replacing years with something else help? It is hard to grasp that number. Our universe came into existence about 13.6 billion years ago. What does human existence mean in this timespan? This is an attempt in trying to build a perspective for the time and in a way, large numbers.
How? Let&amp;rsquo;s try out two methods:
Map large numbers to smaller ones we can relate with.</description></item></channel></rss>